(Leonard:)- No problem.
- I had no idea it was so heavy.
(Leonard:)Thing just fell right over on me,
didn't it? Heh.
(David:)Yeah. Lucky for you it wasn't moving.
- Oh, hey, Leonard. Ooh, are you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)It's just a little motorcycle accident.
Oh, my God. How fast were you going?
I don't know. It was all such a blur.
[CHUCKLES]
(David:)Good one.
He couldn't even get it started.
(David:)- Hi. Dave.
- Hi. Penny. So it's your motorcycle?
- Uh-huh.
- Oh. Is it okay?
(Leonard:)Lucky for the bike it landed on my leg.
- Mind giving me a hand with Speed Racer?
- Oh, yeah. Sure.
(Penny:)So, um, Dave,
how do you know Leonard?
- I'm a physicist.
- Ha, ha. No, you're not.
DAVID:
Why is that so surprising?
PENNY: Well, it's just that the physicists
I know are indoors-y and pale.
LEONARD:
I'm not indoors-y.
(Leonard:)I just wear the appropriate sun block
because I don't take melanoma lightly.